question_data = [
    {
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Typewriter is the longest word that can be typed using only the first row on a QWERTY keyboard.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Coca-Cola&#039;s original colour was green.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "The sum of all the numbers on a roulette wheel is 666.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Furby was released in 1998.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "You are allowed to sell your soul on eBay.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "&quot;Santa Claus&quot; is a variety of melon.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Popcorn was invented in 1871 by Frederick W. Rueckheim in the USA "
                    "where he sold the snack on the streets of Chicago.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "The British organisation CAMRA stands for The Campaign for Real Ale.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "The pickled gherkin was first added to hamburgers "
                    "because a US health law required all fast-food to include a source of Vitamin C.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Instant mashed potatoes were invented by Canadian Edward Asselbergs in 1962.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    }
]
